

APPLY FOR UX/UI DESIGNER

- behance.net/chanvanda
- chanvandaofficail@gmail.com
- **9** 068 485 435
- O Tuek Thlar, Sen Sok, Phnom Penh

Dear. Mr / Madam

I'm applying for the UX/UI Design job. I've worked in this role for over a year, so I've learned a lot. I've gained knowledge from school and online sources, and I've had a helpful mentor who's a senior UX/UI Designer. I've also had the opportunity to be part of several projects that have not only improved my skills but have also made me a strong fit for this job.

In those projects, I have experience with tasks: like User research, User flows, Design System, Wireframe, Prototype, User interface, Icon Design, Illustrator Design, Create Mockup, Graphics Design, and some 3d Design, I have successfully completed these tasks during my dateline.

I'm excited about the chance to work at your company because I think it's the right place for me to learn and grow. I'm ready to work hard and bring my design skills to your team. I'm available for an interview whenever you prefer. Thanks for considering my application, and I'm looking forward to hearing from you soon.

Sincerely,

NEB CHANVANDA





WORK EXPERIENCE



UX/UI Designer

Rizki Digital Connection & Trading Co., LtdJune 2022 to September 2023

- Created wireframes, prototypes, and mockups, design system
- Designed user interfaces web and mobile interface
- Completed design Social Media Interface, Food & Drink Interface, Marketplace Interface
- Completed design Chat Interface
- Illustrate design conception
- Create new graphics design concept
- Conducted User Experience research
- Identify and troubleshoot UX problems with marketing team
- Collaborated with developer to implement designs



Digital Marketing

Goldeneye Gaming Limited (China Company) February 2022 to June 2022

- Promote content NFT and Game on Discord server and Twitter
- Research new related content for company
- Contact with agency company



Digital Marketing | Graphics Design

Farm June (Online Food Sale)

January 2021 to May 2022

- Manage Facebook page
- Boost Page
- Analysis data on Facebook Ads
- · Design Poster
- Sale Reports

- behance.net/chanvanda
- chanvandaofficail@gmail.com
- **9** 068 485 435
- Tuek Thlar, Sen Sok, Phnom Penh

RELEVANT SKILLS

- Graphics Design
- Digital Marketing

DESIGN

- Sketch
- Design Thinking
- Branding Design
- User Flow
- User Interface
- User Research
- Wireframing
- Prototyping

TOOLS & CODE

Figma, Sketch, Adobe Family, Miro, Protopie, Blender, Webflow, Canva, Trello, Html, CSS, Javascript, Reactjs

LANGUAGE

- Native Khmer
- Intermediate English

EDUCATION



TRAINING COURSE



Completed UX Design Foundations

Learn on Uxcel and Google

January 2023 - May 2023

UX/UI Design

Mentor Support

June 2022 - February 2023

Completed Adobe XD, Figma, Sketch, Webflow

Learn from Youtube & Udemy

2020-2021

Completed Coding Skill (C#, Html, CSS , Java,

Javascript, PHP, Python, SQL, Linux, Network, Flutter)

Norton University

2019 - 2023

Completed Ecommerce Dropshipping Skill

(Shopify Store, Product Research, Facebook Ads & Google Ads, Ads Strategy) with Khmer Mentor .

Learn from Mentor and Team

2019 - 2020

Completed Design Course (Adobe Photoshop , Adobe

Illustrator)

Self learning

2019 - 2020

REFERENCE

Mr. Say HengMeng

Senior UX/UI Design at Codingate

Tel: 077 848 677

- behance.net/chanvanda
- chanvandaofficail@gmail.com
- **(3)** +855 68 485 435

CLICK HERE FOR MY
PORTFOLIO